fileadded.com 2011-12-01

# Free Unlimited File Hosting Service | Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

We strongly respect your privacy. All informations collected at Fileadded Free File Hosting will be kept strictly confidential and will not be sold, resued, or rented in any way.

### Logging IP Addresses

For each visitor to our web page, our web server does not recognize any information regarding the domain or email address. IP addresses are logged and used by Fileadded Free File Hosting for measuring usage.

### Collecting Email Addresses

We collect the email addresses of users for the purpose of measuring usage. Fileadded Free File Hosting does not rent, sell, or share personal informations about you with anyone.

### Certain Exceptional Disclosures

We may disclose your informations if necessary to protect our legal rights or if the informations relates to actual or threatened harmful conduct or potential threats to the physical safety of any person. Disclosure may be required by law or if we receive legal processes.

### Use of Cookies

Fileadded Free File Hosting uses cookies to store the preferences of users, only if they so choose.

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).
  * For more information about Doubleclick DART Cookie, please visit [DoubleClick DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx).

### Third-Party Cookies

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertisers may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.

### Third-Party Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, you can go to : **http://www.networkadvertising.org/** .

### Types of Information Collected

We automatically track and collect the following categories of information when you visit our site: (1) IP addresses; (2) domain servers; (3) types of computers accessing the site; and (4) types of web browsers used to access the site. Traffic data is anonymous information that does not personally identify you but is helpful for marketing purposes or for improving your experience on the site.

### Updates and Changes to Privacy Policy

We reserve the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, change, update, or modify this Privacy Policy, simply by posting such change, update, or modification on the site and without any other notice to you. Any such change, update, or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the site.
